https://www.tshirtsunited.com/privacy

Skip to ContentSkip to Main Menu
HomePrivacy & Security PolicyPrivacy & Security Policy This privacy notice explains how we use and look after the personal information we collect from you T34 Limited is the data controller, responsible for processing of any personal data you give us. We take every care to keep your information secure and to prevent any unauthorised access to or use of it.What information do we collect about you? We collect information about you when you make a purchase from us, or when you sign-up for our mailing list. You provide information about yourself when you register as a customer on our site, or during the checkout process as a guest. The information you give us may include your name, address, e-mail address and phone number.
Information relating to usage of our website is collected using cookies. Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behaviour information.Why do we need to collect and use your personal data? We will only use personal data for any purpose for which it has been specifically provided. The primary basis that we intend to use for the processing of your data is for the fulfilment of orders placed with us, updating you about the progress of said orders, and direct marketing campaigns to promote our goods and services. We use your payment information to take payment, give refunds and prevent fraud. We cannot process your orders and fulfil our part of our contract with you without using this information.Who might we share your information with? We will not share your information with, or sell your information to any other organisations. The sole exceptions to this are:We will supply your personal information with a third party should we be legally required to do so (for example, we may occasionally be asked to provide details of specific transactions when a criminal offence such as card fraud is alleged)We pass on your billing address details to our payment providers (WorldPay and PayPal), as without doing this we would not be able to process your payments. Please note that we do not collect or store any card payment details, nor do we ever have access to your payment card information.We pass on the delivery address information that you provide to our delivery providers (Royal Mail and DPD), as without doing this they would be unable to deliver your order.How long do we keep hold of your information? Your personal data should not be held for longer than is required under the terms of our contract or relationship with you - i.e. as long as you remain a customer or retain an account with us. You have the right to request deletion of your personal data. We will comply with this request, subject to any legal obligations we may have to retain it.How can I access the information you hold about me? As a data subject you have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information please write to us using the contact details noted below. We have an obligation to ensure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. Please ask us to correct or remove any information that you think is incorrect.Marketing We would like to send you information about our products and services which may be of interest to you. If you no longer wish to be contacted for marketing purposes, you can unsubscribe at any time. As previously stated, we will never pass your details on to any third parties for use in any marketing.Cookies We use cookies to track visitor use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity. We use a number of different cookies on our site. If you do not know what cookies are, or how to control or delete them, then we recommend you visit http://www.aboutcookies.org for detailed guidance.The list below describe the cookies we use on this site and what we use them for. Currently we operate an 'implied consent' policy which means that we assume you are happy with this usage. If you are not happy, then you should either not use this site, or you should delete the cookies having visited the site, or you should browse the site using your browser's anonymous usage setting (called "Incognito" in Chrome, "Private Browsing" in Firefox and Safari etc.). If you want to delete any cookies that are already on your computer, please refer to the instructions for your file management software to locate the file or directory that stores cookies.Please note that by deleting our cookies or disabling future cookies you may not be able to access certain areas or features of our site.We use cookies to remember your log-in for you and what you've put in the shopping basket. These we deem strictly necessary to the working of the website. If these are disabled then various functionality on the site will be broken.We use Google Analytics to collect information about visitor behaviour on our website. Google Analytics stores information about what pages you visit, how long you are on the site, how you got here and what you click on. This Analytics data is collected via a JavaScript tag in the pages of our site and is not tied to personally identifiable information. We therefore do not collect or store your personal information (e.g. your name or address) so this information cannot be used to identify who you are. You can find out more about Google's position on privacy as regards its analytics service at http://www.google.com/intl/en_uk/analytics/privacyoverview.htmlThere may also be cookies set on your machine by external websites whose services are used on this site. Cookies of this type are the sharing buttons across the site allow visitors to share content onto social networks. Cookies are currently set by AddThis, Twitter and Facebook. In order to implement these buttons, and connect them to the relevant social networks and external sites, there are scripts from domains outside of our website. You should be aware that these sites are likely to be collecting information about what you are doing all around the Internet, including on this website. You should check the respective policies of each of these sites to see how exactly they use your information and to find out how to opt out, or delete, such information.Other websites Our website contains links to other websites and social media platforms. This privacy policy only applies to this website so when you visit links to other websites or engage via social media widgets or buttons you should make yourself aware of their own privacy policies.Changes to our privacy policy We keep our privacy policy under regular review and we will place any updates on this web page (and/or) inform you of any changes when they occur. This privacy policy was last updated on 17 May 2018How to contact us Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy or information we hold about you:TShirtsUnited.com T34 Limited Unit 4 Vernon Trading EstateNew John StreetBlackheathWest MidlandsB62 8HTWebsite SecurityOur website is secured with an SSL Extended Validation (EV) Security Certificate issued by Comodo. SSL is a standard security protocol which establishes encrypted links between a web server and a browser, thereby ensuring that all communication that happens between a web server and browser(s) remains encrypted and hence private. SSL Certificate is today an industry standard that is used by millions of websites worldwide to protect all communication and data that's transmitted online through the websites.Card SecurityWe take security very seriously, which is why we have chosen to use online credit card processing facilities provided by WorldPay.WorldPay are Europe's leading payment service provider. They are responsible for the online card processing of companies such as John Lewis, Disney, Sage and Vodafone. WorldPay have impeccable fraud prevention capabilities and as such are master merchants for Visa and MasterCard.It is now known that Internet transactions through systems such as WorldPay's are inherently more secure than other methods of making purchases in 'cardholder not present' situations such as telesales, or when giving a card to a waiter in a restaurant.Your online purchase from us will take place in real time, and we will never see your credit card details. The entire financial transaction takes place using WorldPay's state-of-the-art security features and it is absolutely impossible for us to access your financial information. None of your card details pass through, or are stored on, our servers. You can have confidence that our online purchasing facilities are secure and safe to use.Our WorldPay facilities are fully secure and use a range of industry standard and WorldPay unique security and fraud prevention systems. The WorldPay network uses 2048-bit encryption, with full 128-bit encryption between the browser and the WorldPay network. WorldPay systems are regularly inspected by the major banks to ensure that system integrity and security are maintained to the highest standards.The WorldPay processing centre is securely linked to many processing banks worldwide, who handle the credit card authorisations online and process the transactions in real time. Thawte, a public Certificate Authority, certifies the WorldPay servers. Thawte will only issue Digital Certificates to those servers that meet stringent security requirements. The WorldPay servers meet and exceed these requirements. Thank you for signing up to the newsletter.Sorry, something went wrong. Please try again.
TShirtsUnited LoginRegister
Wish List
0
Christmas 2020
Catalogue
SPECIAL OFFERSManchester UnitedCurrent United PlayersManchester and SalfordManchester United LegendsThe Enemy: United's RivalsUnited PhilosophyRetro Manchester UnitedManchester United SongsThe TrebleUnited Line-UpsTitles, Cups & SilverwareMusic T-ShirtsHadrian Richards United ArtworkFace MasksSnoodsMugsLeather WalletsPrintsBest SellersWhat's New?
Clothing
Men'sWomen'sKid'sHooded-TopsSweatshirts
Accessories
SnoodsFace MasksBobble HatsWalletsMugsPrintsBlogAboutContact
